There are a million in one skills and
plugins that claim to solve Claude's
front-end design problem. But as someone
who has tested literally hundreds of
them, there is one that stands above the
rest and it just got a huge upgrade.
Now, I'm talking about Impeccable 4.0
and it is the king of giving Claude Code
the power to create front-end designs
and web designs that actually look good
and give you control while you do it.
So, in this video, I'm going to break
down what this tool is, how it works,
and how you can get the most out of this
thing, so you can start building
front-end designs you actually like.
Now, in my last design related video, we
touched on impeccable a little bit, but
that was in the greater scheme of how to
essentially inject taste into your web
design process so we can get away from
generic AI slop outputs. If you haven't
watched that video, I highly suggest you
do because I'm not going to repeat all
the baseline things you need to
understand when it comes to injecting
your taste and sort of avoiding AI slop
from a design process and instead we're
going to be deep diving impeccable as a
specific tool. Now, there will be some
overlap, but it helps to have that
background coming into this. Now, before
we do a full deep dive on the tool
itself, let's talk about some of the
changes because chances are there's a
lot of you out there who used this tool
a few months ago and are now wondering,
okay, it's 4.0. actually changed here.
Now, the biggest change over the last
few months is live mode. Now, this was
something that was sort of in the alpha
when they're in their 2.0 range, and now
it's gotten a lot more fleshed out. It's
much smoother. It's much snappier, and
allows us again to get outside of the
terminal and start iterating visually,
which makes the design process so much
more simple. The other big change is
worlds. They talk about adding 177 high
rated worlds into this skill. Now, what
the heck does that mean? Well, that
means they've essentially created
177 different design templates,
different aesthetics that you can use
when you're trying to create your
website from scratch. So, kind of like
what we did manually in the last video,
Impeccable is going to show you a the
first sort of design idea it has, and
then it's going to give you a few other
options that are wildly different. Now,
they have a whole article about how they
essentially created this to make sure it
isn't just like slob trash every single
time. I'm not going to dive that into
here because it's going to be like a
15-minute discussion. But what it gives
us is options and options that we can
see visually. And when we hook up
something like the Higsfield MCP to
this, we can actually see what it would
look like with our specific website. And
you'll see that later. That way, it
isn't just like a generic template.
You'd see like what your thing would
look like in these different sort of
visual themes. And those two things, the
live mode in the world are the biggest
differences over the last few months.
And I don't think they're small things
because they're all about iteration and
giving us options throughout the design
process. Now, let's do a quick rundown
of Impeccable itself because there's
probably some of you who've never even
used this app. So, what the heck are we
even talking about here? Well,
Impeccable is a free open- source skill.
It's got about 50,000 stars on GitHub.
GitHub themselves actually integrated it
into their own AI tool because they
liked it so much. And the thesis of the
skill is we want to identify AI slot
patterns. They consider like 40
different things to be AI slot. things
like purple gradients, blue gradients,
that sort of thing. And instead, we
replace those with essentially better
design, so to speak. Impeccable itself
is one skill, but includes 23 different
commands that hit different parts of the
design continuum. This includes things
like shape, polish, making it choir,
animating things, things for onboarding,
coloring, type set, on and on and on.
Now, while each of those things does
something slightly different, the point
is this, and you can see this over here
on the right. Claude gives us something
that's kind of generic, kind of boring.
and we automatically know it's AI.
Impeccable gives us something that is
cleaner, less generic, and overall
better for the user. As for those 23
different commands, well, if we go to
the website itself, which is
impeccable.style, you can see all of
them in action. So, you know, we have
clawed code version here, impeccable
version here. You can see that for each
and every one to get sort of visual idea
of what these things actually do. The
documentation on the website goes pretty
deep and I actually misspoke earlier in
terms of AI slop. There's actually 64
different patterns that they say expose
AI defaults and production defects. And
you can see how this has changed over
the years. Like we all remember this
like the early days of chat GPT, right?
And now you know AI slop looks something
a little bit more like this still. These
are things we want to move away from. So
that's impeccable in a nutshell.
Identify slob and then gives us better
options that allow us to iterate and
even iterate visually with their live
tool. Now to actually use this thing,
it's pretty simple to install. is just
going to be npx impeccable install. Now,
if that is too confusing, you can also
go to the impeccable impeccable GitHub
page. You can copy this URL, paste it
into cloud code and say, "Hey, can you
go ahead and install impeccable for me?"
Now, once you install impeccable, the
other thing you're going to want to
install, like I talked about earlier, is
the Higsfield MCP, which Impeccable is
going to be able to call on when it
builds that worlds feature for us, or
essentially shows us all the different
aesthetic styles for our website. Now,
to get the Higsfield MCP set up, which
again is an aggregator for essentially
every AI image of video generator out
there, you'll just go to higsfield.ai,
go up here to the top where it says MCP
and CLI. Head here to clawed code and
you can just copy this prompt right here
and it will walk you through the
authentication process. After that, the
first step we are going to do is simply
run impeccable in it. And in this case,
I've opened up a new folder and I've
just called it impecc. You can create
whatever folder or directory you want,
but for/impeckable in it. And once you
do that, it's going to begin asking
questions about what it is you're trying
to build. So, I'm going to say I'm
building a real landing page. Then we'll
ask what stack this project should use.
If you don't know, you can just have it
say you're a call. And that's what we'll
do for today. And then it's going to ask
about evidence essentially like what do
you want to be on this website? If you
have screenshots you can provide, if you
have actual numbers, that's great. If
you don't have anything else, you can
essentially tell it to make it all up.
So I just told it to create fake data
for now and we can see what it comes
back with and we can always edit it
later. So after we answered those
questions, impeccable then called on the
Higsfield MCP to create those different
worlds. Essentially those different
design aesthetics for our web page and
it's asking us which one we want to
choose. What it does is it brings it up
in local host so you can actually see
it. So it looks something like this. So
this was the first one that it came up
with. This is essentially be the hero
section for Pathfinder. And then we see
all these other options. Again, this is
very reminiscent to what we did in the
last video. We're like, "Hey, come up
with the different options for us so we
can actually see it." So, we have this
one, we have this one. And again, this
is just like kind of like a highle
sketch of what it would look like and
where you want to go. We have the option
if we don't like these, we can reroll it
down here on the right. We also can give
it an optional steer. So, we could say
like, "Hey, I kind of like number three,
but let's do some more variations of
that." add or something to that effect.
In this case, what we're doing of these,
I kind of like the first one it came up
with. So, I'm just going to say build
this. So, I just click this and that's
going to get sent back to the terminal.
And so now, it's going to start building
out the prototype of that landing page
in that style we chose. And as part of
that build process, it's then going to
show us multiple variations of that
specific style. So, we have at the
beginning a bunch of different styles.
We choose one style and now we have
variations of that style. So it gives us
the constellation option. It gives us
sort of the dossier split and then sort
of the find the Y. Again, just like
before, if we want to give it an
optional steer, I have sort of a prompt
window down here that I can point it to.
But for this, I kind of like um I think
what we'll do is we'll go with number
three and we'll say build this. You can
see here in the terminal, it got passed.
It says timeline approved. Recording the
approval in the surface brief, then
loading the craft floor and building.
And this is what I like about
impeccable, the fact that it's very
visual in terms of how we make the
decisions. And at every step of the way,
we have the option to steer it. It's not
an extremely prescriptive skill. And
you've seen those where it's like, okay,
here's random skill from random GitHub
repo. The website it makes is really
cool looking, but that's like the only
type of website it can create. It's kind
of like a one-trick pony. Things like
Impeccable are very general, which means
I think it has a lower floor. like these
very sort of onetrick pony skills will
always give you a pretty cool website
but it's just that kind impeccable a lot
more room for error on your part but we
can make it much more customized and in
the end if we actually work on it I
think you end up getting a better
product so Impeccable actually finished
creating the website and what it does at
the end of the first iteration is it
launches a sub agent called the
impeccable finish reviewer so it's
essentially checking everything to make
sure in the process of building this
thing we didn't actually, you know, sort
of trip over ourselves and add some
quote unquote AI slot pattern. So, it
does an additional run through with a
separate sub agent that it's fresh
context window. So, it's supposed to be
a second set of eyes to make sure what
we set out to build is what we actually
build. So, here's the website it built
us. And remember, we gave impeccable
very little information. I just said,
"Hey, I want it to be Pathfinder." I
gave it no reference images. I really
even didn't even give it a CTA. I just
said, "This is a fake AI analytics
company. Create some information for
it." And this is what we got. And if you
compare this to what we would have got
with the same sort of prompt if we just
use like the front end design skill, the
outputs are wildly different. Mainly,
this isn't the kind of generic output
you would see. Now, is this great? Is
this exactly what we want on a oneshot?
Probably not. But I think when we do any
sort of creative work with AI and
Claude, I think you really have to get
away from the idea of like this must be
a oneshot thing. It always is an
iterative process, which is why the
impeccable live feature is so nice. So
to use the impeccable live feature,
we're just going to do impeccable
forward slash and then do live and it's
going to bring it up for us. Now once we
do that, it'll bring the website back up
and we'll have this little bar down
here. Now what you're going to want to
use mostly is the pick element thing
which we see right down here. So you
know I have insert but I can click pick
and I can see all the different
components. So let's say I want to
adjust this. I click on it and I have a
prompt window. Now I can add anything I
want here and I can see how many
variations I want. You can have one
variation, two variations all the way up
to four. You can also do a microphone.
You can also choose exactly what it is
you want to do. So let's say if I wanted
to make it bolder or quieter or do
polish or type set those specific sort
of domains, we can specify that as well.
Now remember these are all related to
like the impeccable commands. And if I
go back to the impeccable website, I can
see them all here, right? You know, uh
quieter, overdrive, characterize, you
know, all these sort of things. Okay, so
if you're like, uh, what exactly is it
asking me? What does this do? Just check
here. So, let's say I just wanted to
make this bolder, right? Uh, I just want
to make a bolder. I don't even have to
give it a prompt, and I want three
different variations. I'm just going to
click that, hit enter, and it's going to
start generating the variants. And if
you hop back into the terminal, you will
see that command sent there because the
session you're in is always going to be
pulling for live mode events. Now, while
that's working, let's talk about what
else is going on in here. So, we have
the detect button that will detect
essentially any of those AI slop
antiatterns. If you're doing this from
scratch, I kind of already did that in
the creation process. This is more for
if you're using Impeccable Live on a
website you've already generated. We
have the design MD. I'll move this over
a little bit. And this is our entire
design file. All of our colors,
components, what we're doing for our
buttons. Again, very similar to uh
Google Stitch and also what you see
these days inside of Flaw Design. We can
also see the actual raw file if we want
that as well. We also have the ability
to insert things. And we have a prompt
window here as well, which is you
steering the page. So, this is pretty
much exactly the same as if you had the
terminal up and you're saying, "Hey,
let's do X, Y, and Z a little bit
differently versus trying to pick a
specific component and doing sort of
these three variants that I just showed
you." And speaking of those three
variants, here's what it gave us when we
told it to make it bolder. So, this is
variation one.
Variation two, we kind of added just
like the red line. And then we have
variation three. But we have the ability
to tune these things as well. So I can
kind of mess with the tilt. Do I want
the stamp border on and off? So not only
do I have three variations, I have
variations of each variation, which I
honestly love versus having to prompt
Claude Code to create some sort of like
micro tweak section on its own. And once
you like it, all you have to do is hit
accept. And again, what is that going to
do? It's just going to send that
information back to the terminal. Now,
at this point, all that is left is to
iterate, iterate, iterate. Now, we don't
have to do everything inside of
Impeccable Live, even though that's what
I've been showcasing. The use case for
Impeccable Live is what you have seen,
which is for micro adjustments and
variations in specific components. If we
want to think big picture, we want big
big layout changes or just completely go
in another direction, we're going to
want to use the terminal for that. So,
if that's the case, let's say I didn't
like this design at all. I was like,
hey, like we did the variations, turns
out this just isn't what I like. Well,
let's just do what we would normally do
inside of a design process and feed it
some different references. So, this
right here is sort of my inspiration
library of all these different sort of
hero pages and designs that I've liked
and I've seen across the web. So, if I
wanted to now have a new variation that
looks something like this, well, what
I'm going to do is I'm just going to
point Claude code at this library or
drop in the screenshot and say, hey,
let's try a new variation, something
that looks like this. So, let's say we
instead wanted to go with like this ASC2
sort of like web section, this like kind
of vibe we're going for. So I can just
copy this image. I'm going to paste this
in. Now I'm just going to give it a
prompt like so. So take a look at this
reference image I gave you. This is also
inside of my taste vault. This is
currently running on the 4610
local host port. I kind of want to go in
a new direction with sort of the landing
page we've created. I want to go with
this like ASC2 type style. Remember we
still have access to the Higfield MCP.
So if we need to create assets for the
background hero page, we can do that as
well. But go ahead and create a
variation like that. And so again, this
is a huge sweeping change. Not something
we would necessarily use the live thing
for. And here's the second version of
our website. Again, a huge departure
from what we saw before. Definitely has
an ASC2 theme based on our reference,
but this is still an impeccable based
product. It ran the impeccable reviewer,
made sure there wasn't slop, and so
we're able to kind of get the best of
both worlds in this case. And just like
you saw before, we could again bring up
impeccable live. We could start doing
things. I think something that would
look cool is if we ran essentially like
the animate um thing on each one of
these sections to give it a little bit
little bit of movement so it isn't so
static. But this is kind of how you want
to approach it. Big picture, the lion
claw code, small picture, really start
knocking out stuff with impeccable. And
actually, now that I look at this, there
is some motion and some of the numbers
coming in and out on this hero if you
look closely. So, that's where I'm going
to leave you guys for today. Impeccable
is a great tool in your toolbox for any
sort of front-end design work, and as
you saw, you can actually get pretty far
if you stay 100% within the impeccable
ecosystem. I think the best use case for
it is a more, you know, sort of
wide-ranging design approach that brings
in outside sources like references that
we saw at the end. And that whole sort
of workflow is what I detailed, you
know, step by step in my last video
about how to sort of defeat AI slop. But
I think it was nice to sort of do a deep
dive on what I think is the best front
end design skill in the game right now.
So, as always, let me know what you
thought. Make sure to check out Chase AI
Plus if you want to get your hands on my
Claude Code Masterass. It's actually
going to have a huge update coming out
this week, which is exciting. And other
than that, I'll see you